Finding aid for the Barbara Morgan Wight Gallery Collection LSC.1872
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Southwest Series., 1928-1929.
  - Willard Morgan with Leica Model A Camera, Bandelier National Monument New Mexico., Date Taken: 1929. Date Printed: 1971.; Dimensions: 12 3/4" x 9 7/8 on 19" x 16" (Box 8, Folder 20)
- Packing instructions., undated.
  - Packing slips., Date Taken: undated. (Box 5, Folder 21)
    Contains 4 boards with return packing instructions. Likely to be slips leftover from exhibitions.